(Howard:)Yeah, but we
weren't...
(Howard:)I-I mean, you
and I never...
(Bernadette:)Had sex?
(Leonard:)Yeah.
(Bernadette:)Well, whose fault was that?
(Penny:)Complimentary nachos!
(Penny:)You enjoy.
(Penny:)Never had sex? Wow.
(Howard:)What do you mean,
whose fault was that?
(Bernadette:)Well, we could've
been having sex,
(Bernadette:)but you never made the move.
(Howard:)I didn't think you wanted me
to make the move.
(Bernadette:)Howard, a girl doesn't go out
with a man like you,
(Bernadette:)with your looks,
your fancy patter
(Bernadette:)and your tight hoochie pants
if she's not expecting him
(Bernadette:)to eventually make the move.
(Penny:)Really?
(Bernadette:)Really.
(Howard:)Son of a bitch.
(Penny:)Hey, this is a little awkward,
but my manager says
(Penny:)I can't actually
give nachos away.
(Penny:)So... just take that
when you're ready.
(Howard:)Yeah, we had
a really great talk,
(Howard:)and we're gonna start
seeing each other again.